question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pencil&#039;s lead is typically made from graphite, not lead",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Crystal Pepsi was first sold in US markets in 1993.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Kraft &quot;Cheez Whiz&quot; contains cheese culture, but doesn&#039;t actually contain cheese",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]